airinstaller.com 2016-11-05

# Privacy | Air Installer

### User Privacy

Air Installer is dedicated to protecting our user’s privacy. We’ve built this privacy portal in order to educate our consumers and advertisers on what information we collect and also how it is used and stored.

#### Information We Collect & How We Use It

  * **IP Address** We use your IP address to tailor the in-path install offers to your geographic location. Some of our advertisers only want USA installs of their software, therefore we only show users in the USA those offers.
  * **Machine ID** Your computer has a _machine id_ which is tracked to make sure we do not show you in-path ads for the same product twice.
  * **Language** If your computer is using an English based keyboard, we’re not going to show French software ads!

We may use cookies to track your browsing activity across our web properties and software. This is only used in aggregate format (non personally identifiable) for analytics purposes, or to improve our websites.

We will never ask for your name, email, address, or any other personal information. We don’t need this information, we don’t want this information, and advise you to never enter such information online unless you’re familiar with the company and using a secure connection.

* * *

### Advertiser & Affiliate Privacy

Thank you for visiting Airinstaller.com (the “Site”). The Site is an Internet property of Air Installer and its affiliated companies (“Air Installer”, “our”, “we” or “us”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) outlines the privacy practices and policies associated with the Site and in relation to any information that you may share with us when you access and use the Site.

**1\. Personal Information**

When you purchase, download trial or evaluation versions, or register for any software products and/or services made available through the Site, we may collect personal information that you submit including without limitation your name, address, electronic mail (email) address, phone number, and credit card information (collectively, your “Personal Information”) for the purposes of recording the transaction when you engage in activities on the Site or within the software products or services. If and when we use a third party payment processing merchant, we ensure that the same privacy criteria as defined herein are in place with such merchant. We do not (knowingly) collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. We also give users the option of receiving useful product information (such as software product or service updates, and associated product and service offerings), via email. We fully ensure your privacy and value your trust. We will never sell, rent, lease or trade your personal information to any third party. Likewise, your information will not be shared with a third party in any other way unless we are required to do so in order to complete a transaction initiated by you or as required to be disclosed by law or to an applicable regulatory or governing body. Air Installer may engage the services of a third party from time to time and may be required to provide certain information that includes your personal information in order for the third party to perform such services. Any third parties who provide services to Air Installer have agreed not to disclose your information or use it for any other purpose, and are required to implement or adopt a Privacy Policy that is no less stringent than this Privacy Policy. If you are receiving email communications from Air Installer, you may opt-out of receiving emails from us at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the email or by visiting our website at airinstaller.com. By choosing to enter and submit the requested information when prompted, you are consenting to our collection, use, and disclosure of such information for the purposes as outlined herein.

**2\. Anonymous Information**

“Anonymous Information” is information other than Personal Information, and includes the domain names, IP addresses and type of browsers that you may use, referring URLs, and other, non-personally identifiable information.

When you access any site or service covered by this Privacy Policy, we collect Anonymous Information. We use this information for system administration, for market research (which may be shared with third parties), to personalize your experience at our site, to show you more relevant advertising messages, and, generally, to improve our products and/or services. We share this Anonymous Information with selected third parties and business partners in order to deliver to you more relevant advertising messages.

Air Installer will not share any Anonymous Information if that information is or will be linked to your Personal Information, unless we have given you notice as described above and you have given us authorization to do so.

Air Installer can and will use IP addresses to identify users of our site when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site’s policies, or to protect our products, services, site, or other users.

**3\. Sharing Personal Information**

We will not share your Personal Information unless we have first given you notice that we might share your data, and you have authorized us to do so. Our business partners who receive information from us have the right to use the data we provide them (sometimes, in connection with other information they may have gathered about you), but are generally prohibited from sharing this information with other companies or people.

In certain special cases, we may disclose your Personal Information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or otherwise injuring or interfering with Air Installer’ rights, property or operations, other Air Installer users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your Personal Information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation.

Finally, where, in our sole discretion after undertaking such investigation or investigations as we see fit, we determine that you have engaged in conduct which might be considered, unlawful, fraudulent, or which might bring the reputation or standing of Air Installer into disrepute either with the general public or with a business partner or potential business partner of Air Installer, we reserve the right to release your Personal Information to such persons or third parties as we consider necessary in order to prevent you from causing injury to, or otherwise injuring or interfering, now or in the future, with Air Installer’ rights, property or operations or otherwise the rights, property or operations of anyone else who could be harmed by such conduct.

**4\. Third Party Relationships**

Third Party Links. The Site, software products, and services may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites and, where you request information from third party providers, Air Installer may transfer you directly to the websites of such third party providers. Air Installer is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Air Installer has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such website. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with Air Installer.

Third Party Offers. Air Installer may provide its users with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from third parties. Where you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a third party during the applicable information collection process, your personally identifiable information that was provided during that Air Installer information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide their products and/or services to you so that you do not have to complete another information collection form to purchase or receive that product or service.

**5\. Opt-out Unsubscribe**

When you submit your information through the Site, you have opted-in to receive information and future communications from us. To opt-out of having future email communications from us, please contact [privacy@airinstaller.com](mailto:privacy@getwebbar.com) or follow the opt-out request process in the applicable email communication. When you submit personally identifiable information through the Site to receive information and marketing communications from any third party providers, you may be contacted by these third party providers. If you do not wish to receive future communications from the third party providers, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding the use of your information. To opt-out of having future third party marketing communications sent to you, you will be required to unsubscribe with the applicable third party providers.

**6\. Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**7\. Children’s Online Protection Act**

In compliance with the Children’s Online Protection Act of 2013 (COPPA), Air Installer never knowingly collects, maintains or shares the information of children under the age of 13. We take the protection of children’s privacy very seriously, and any user under 13 years of age is strictly prohibited from using any Air Installer website, software or service.

**8\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Notice regarding any Privacy Policy changes will be placed in a prominent location on the Site and will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

**9\. Contacting Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us:

For further information, please review our [ Network Guidelines](http://airinstaller.com/network-guidelines).
